ADDY OSMANI: So the other week, I bought a new Windows laptop.
上周，我买了一台新的Windows笔记本电脑。
MATT GAUNT: How come?
怎么了
ADDY OSMANI: I was curious whether-- it's
我很好奇
been a few years since I've really used Windows heavily,
几年来我没有广泛使用Windows
and I was curious what the front-end workflow
我很想知道前端工作流程的形状
and the command line workflow looked like there.
命令行工作流程。
MATT GAUNT: So what does the front-end tooling
那么前端工具系统现在是什么样？
ADDY OSMANI: So the command line workflow--
命令行工作流程-
the front-end tooling workflow isn't massively different,
前端工具的工作流程没有太大不同，
but to get your command line workflow on par these days
但是现在这些天在适当级别获得命令行工作流程
still requires a little bit of work.
仍然需要一点工作。
So what I was used to when I played with Windows a few years
几年前我在Windows上工作时所习惯的
ago was the Windows prompt, which
这是Windows提示
was this really very, very basic update to the DOS prompt.
这是对DOS提示符的原始更新。
Always seemed like better for just managing
仅仅管理起来似乎总是更好
files than anything--
文件比什么都重要
MATT GAUNT: Yeah, in some ways--
是的，以某种方式--非常认真。
and that was about it.
仅此而已。
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah, I'd play with utilities there and stuff.
是的，我在那儿尝试实用程序
But Microsoft then did PowerShell,
微软随后启动了PowerShell，
which was way better and designed for automation,
哪个更好，更适合自动化
had much better support for objects and variables,
为对象和变量提供更好的支持
and had these really rich prompts for commandlets.
它包含有价值的快捷方式指令
But it comes with support for auto-completion right out
但它具有自动完成功能支持-
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
ADDY OSMANI: --so that's what I want from--
-那就是我想要的
MATT GAUNT: It's the kind of thing that you can--
这是一件事-
ADDY OSMANI: --a shell.
-巧合。
MATT GAUNT: --take for granted with things
-不要以OS X和Linux之类的东西来重视它。
And it's like their terminals just come with all that stuff.
他们的终端配备了所有这些东西
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah.
是的
MATT GAUNT: It's just stock.
只是股票而已。
And so another thing that we commonly do on Mac
我们通常在Mac上做的另一件事
is we have dot files set up with all of our aliases.
是我们安装了带有所有别名的点文件。
And you can create your own PowerShell profile
您可以创建自己的PowerShell页面
that's got the same type of stuff set up.
安装相同的东西。
MATT GAUNT: OK.
知道了
ADDY OSMANI: So you can create aliases for Sublime Text.
您可以为Sublime Text创建别名。
So subl or ST will go and fire off Sublime.
subl或ST将运行Sublime。
So you can create system-level aliases.
您可以创建系统范围的别名。
You can use DOS key as well, which
也可以使用Doskey
is another utility for just creating aliases.
它是用于创建别名的另一个工具包。
But PowerShell's great.
但是PowerShell很棒。
It doesn't quite get you all the way.
还不够。
There's still a few things missing, so--
有些事情还不完整。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
ADDY OSMANI: Another tool that I use
我使用的另一个工具
is ConEmu, which is a console emulator.
是控制台模拟器ConEmu。
And it's got support for multiple tabs.
支持多个标签。
So you've got multiple tabs in there.
您有多个标签。
You can do vertical tab splitting as well and all
您还可以垂直拆分选项卡
sorts of other layout--
各种类型的等等
MATT GAUNT: That's quite nice.
很好
ADDY OSMANI: --configs.
-调整布局。
MATT GAUNT: Again, it still feels like you're-- it's just
再一次，我感觉-
things that I've grown to expect, I guess, or one--
我认为这是我曾经期望的事情，或者-
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah.
是的
MATT GAUNT: It's one of those things.
这是其中之一
If it was removed from me, I'd probably instantly just
如果从我这里带走，它将立即开始
be like, please can I have the tabs back now.
要求她回来。
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah.
是的
ADDY OSMANI: So I use ConEmu, but there's still
我正在使用ConEmu，但仍在
other things missing.
其他事情不完整。
So the tool that I mostly use these days is Cmder.
这些天我最常用的工具是Cmder。
And Cmder is awesome.
Cmder很棒。
MATT GAUNT: Why is it awesome?
为什么很棒？
ADDY OSMANI: Because I said so.
因为我说过
It's awesome because it's like a power
超级强大的工具包
utility with all of this stuff.
因为它包含所有这些东西。
So it's got ConEmu, it's got PowerShell.
它的ConEmu及其PowerShell。
It's using all that stuff.
使用所有这些东西。
MATT GAUNT: Oh, it's just like a group of all the best things--
哦，这是一堆最好的东西-是的。
ADDY OSMANI: Yes.
-一包。
ADDY OSMANI: Exactly.
没错
It's also got Clink, which is-- basically,
它还包含Clink-基本上是
it's the Windows Shell combined with Readline, which is a GNU
Windows Shell与Readline集成在一起，后者是一个库
library for working with Dash.
GNU与Dash合作。
Gives you better auto-completion,
为您提供更好的自动完成功能
gives you history search, batch utilities.
为您提供历史记录搜索和Bash工具包。
MATT GAUNT: Nice.
好漂亮
ADDY OSMANI: Really nice.
很漂亮
And my favorite thing about Cmder
我最喜欢Cmder的地方
is the integration that you can set up with other apps.
它是可以与其他应用程序一起安装的集成。
So something I've tried to do over the last couple of years
过去两年来我一直在尝试做的事情
with Sublime is try to get my editor
使用Sublime试图将编辑器与屏幕上的命令行结合起来，
MATT GAUNT: --just somewhere else--
-就在其他地方--包括在内
ADDY OSMANI: --built in.
-在UI中，是的。
ADDY OSMANI: And none of the integrations I've ever seen
没有积分出现
have looked half decent.
我认为合适。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
I tried one plug-in on Atom, and it was just-- it sort of
我在Atom上尝试了一个插件，它是-
looked like my terminal, but it wasn't quite.
有点像我的终端机，但不完全是。
And it was a bit clunky.
有点烦人。
ADDY OSMANI: Yep.
是的
So this just adds it in.
这添加了它们。
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah, it just adds it in.
是的，他补充说。
You have a single window, drag it around.
您有一个窗口，将其拖动。
You've got your command line at the top,
您上面有命令行
you've got your Complete Editor window at the bottom.
以及下面的“完整编辑器”窗口。
MATT GAUNT: Nice.
真可爱-它是完全可配置的。
So you can tell it to take up how much of the command line
您可以订购它来占用您想要的空间
window you want.
从命令行窗口。
You can script that.
你可以写她的文字。
MATT GAUNT: I like it, yep.
我喜欢，是的。
ADDY OSMANI: It's kind of neat.
很好
So you've got that.
那就是我们所拥有的。
Cmder also encourages you to install PoshGit--
Cmder还鼓励您安装PoshGit-
MATT GAUNT: OK.
知道了
ADDY OSMANI: --which is a set of utilities on top of Git.
它是基于Git的工具包。
So if I go and I clone a project on GitHub and I CD into it,
如果您在GitHub上复制项目并输入cd命令
I can make some edits and do Gits and type
我可以做一些修改并制作Git。
in a command like Git C. And then
然后输入类似Git C的命令。
I can tab through all the options like Commit
我可以浏览诸如“提交”之类的所有选项
and all of that other stuff.
还有其他所有东西。
MATT GAUNT: Nice.
真漂亮-好可爱
Nice contextual auto-completion.
不错的上下文自动完成功能。
MATT GAUNT: Nice little bit of sugar on top.
像糖果上的装饰品。
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah, exactly.
是的，完全正确。
What do you think about Package Managers?
您如何看待软件包管理器？
Could you use another one in your life?
您是否还想要一个？
MATT GAUNT: No.
没有。
I've got AptGet on Linux and that, to me,
我在Linux上有AptGet
just makes total sense.
这对我来说很有意义。
Home brew is the closest thing, I think, on Mac that I have.
我认为Homebrew是我最接近Mac的东西
But then it has its own weird oddities on my machines
另一方面，我的设备有些奇怪
normally.
和往常一样。
ADDY OSMANI: I'm hearing that you want another package
我听说您想要另一个包管理器。
MATT GAUNT: You're hearing me wrong, but fine.
你听不太清楚，但是还可以。
ADDY OSMANI: So you want another package manager,
所以你想要另一个小组经理，
and Windows has got one.
Windows有一个。
MATT GAUNT: OK.
知道了
ADDY OSMANI: It's called Chocolately.
叫做巧克力味。
MATT GAUNT: That just doesn't sound like a package manager,
这似乎不像数据包管理器。
but fine.
但是，好吧。
How is Chocolately?
巧克力味如何？
Is it good?
好吗
ADDY OSMANI: Chocolately is decent.
体面的巧克力味。
You're using Atom.
您正在使用Atom。
You've got your hipster sticker over there.
并把这张时髦的海报。
MATT GAUNT: My little arm sticker, yeah.
-是我手臂上的小贴纸。是的，你有你的海报。
So you can do like choco install atom.
您可以输入：choco install atom。
Just install.
只需安装。
It gives you an update, progress bar, and your command line
向您显示更新，进度栏和命令行
and everything.
还有一切。
MATT GAUNT: To be fair, with things
公平地说，这种
like that, the minute you start getting used to it,
事情一开始我就习惯了
it's really, really nice.
我真的很好。
I don't know.
不知道
It's nice not having to go to a website, download the thing,
很高兴不必进入站点然后下载东西
open up the AC, and then do all the other stuff,
并打开AC，然后执行所有其他操作。
so that's nice.
很好
Does it update as well?
它也在发生吗？
ADDY OSMANI: I think so.
我也这么认为
MATT GAUNT: Nice.
好漂亮